This is Telgram.
The messaging app that our solution integrates.
We can search our contacts and talk to them.
We can send all type of files.
If we want create a group with several contacts,
we must press New Group,
write the name,
and select the contacts.
And we have a group with the funcionality of the previous chat.
This is Favro.
The app that our solution integrates
for kanban management, sprint management and calendar management.
To create a kanban board,
we must press collections
and select kanban.
We can add a task to the backlog.
To put this task on the kanban board,
to assing the task to someone
And to move it over the board as it progress.
We can also edit the task date.
And vizualize it in the calendar
where we can see clearly the timeline of the task.
This is Bitbucket,
the app that our solution integrates
for version control and
classification of documents by directory.
We can create a new repository if we press "+" button.
Once done, we can clone it in our local respository
from we can upload all our files.
Once uploaded,
we can check that the document is in the remote repository.
To check all our respositorys that we have opened,
we simply press on "repository".
This is Skype,
the video call app that our solution integrate.
If we wanted to create a group,
we just must to click here,
we write the name to look for
and select the participant we want talk with,
and click "ready".
To start a call, we can press here
if we want an audio call.
or here, if we want a video call.
Call is starting.
Hello!
Hi, what'up?
As we can see, audio is working perfectly.
Skype have several options,
like to stop video or audio.
We are goint to end the call.